+386 41 645256 → erika@serox.si → ercchy.github.com

#### PROFILE

Driven professional with broad technical skills which include design and development of web applications and a good knowledge of implementing backend solutions. I think of myself as highly resourceful, innovative, and competent software engineer. Strengths include:

- Python / Django / JavaScript
- Full cycle software development
- Driven to solve problems

- Web development, responsive design
- Excellent communication skills
- Great ability to multitask

I have a passion for software development and would like to further myself in software development, user experience design (UX), agile practices and teams. I invest heavily into my knowledge outside of regular work and it is not unusual of me to take a UX/HCI course at Coursera or attend a conference like EuroPython.

### ■ TECHNICAL SKILLS

**Languages:** Python, Javascript, PHP, Java, C#

**Frameworks:** Django, JavaScriptMVC, CanJS, jQuery, Wordpress, Joomla

**Methodologies:** OOP, TDD, Agile development

**Version control:** git, github, bitbucket, subversion

Web development: HTML5, CSS3, responsive design, OOCSS, SASS, LESS,

Bootstrap, UX design, Gimp, Adobe Fireworks

**Tools (IDE):** PyCharm, Eclipse, Sublime Text 2

**Operating systems:** Linux (ubuntu, Amazon Linux), Windows

**Databases:** MySQL, AWS RDS MySQL, Toad for MySQL

Other: Amazon Web Services (AWS): console, AMIs, EC2, SES and

use of boto python library for AWS,

automated deployment: fabric and ansible and continuous

integration with Travis-CI

Familiar with concepts like PaaS, SaaS, laaS and different

cloud vendors

Knowledge of telecom domain: sales processes, ordering and

fulfillment, monthly billing and customer support

Volunteering at a local coding events and clubs as a mentor

+386 41 645256 → erika@serox.si → ercchy.github.com

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Peer 2 Peer University, San Francisco, USA (telecommute)
Software engineer (March 2013 - present)

Developed software to offer more qualitative support for learners and facilitators of education courses.

- Designed and implemented online assessment system to complement offered open courses.
- Usability testing and research about new open source services,
- Wordpress theme development for partners

Technologies used: Python, Django, Javascript, Amazon Web Services EC2, South, Ansible, SASS, Travis-CI, Twitter Bootstrap, Wordpress.

Petra Marketing d.o.o., Ljubljana / Si.Mobil d.d. Ljubljana, Slovenia Software engineer (February 2011 - March 2013)

Developed solutions to support cloud services platform offered by second largest telecom company in Slovenia (Si.Mobil).

- Designed and implemented marketplace web application that enables end-customers to order cloud services and get support,
- Designed, developed and implemented a web application to support sales processes. It includes functionality to manage accounts, lookup product price lists, product documentation, creation of quotes, required documentation generation in PDF, analytics and reporting,
- Provided support to telecom and their end-customers on how to use cloud applications and services (in-person or remote).

Technologies used: Python, Django, Amazon Web Services EC2, SES, boto, South, Fabric, django-compressor, janrain social login, crispy forms, HTML5 boilerplate, Twitter Bootstrap, LESS, Google Apps, Google Charts, various cloud vendors.

Redox d.o.o., Portorose, Slovenia

Application support engineer (September 2008 - January 2011)

Developed features and provided support for radio broadcasting digital audio solution and marinas prepaid system.

- Development of a server application of prepaid system for marinas. Application enabled visitors to marinas to use their amenities simply with a prepaid card,
- Designed and implemented a component for CMS system to enable radio stations to get

# **ERIKA POGORELC**

+386 41 645256 ♦ erika@serox.si ♦ ercchy.github.com

access to schedules and forward them to their listeners,

Technologies used: Java, sockets, PHP, Joomla, MySQL, CVS.

# **Prior to September 2008**

I gained work experience working in non-IT related fields like charity organisation and sales department. More information available upon request.

# EDUCATION

# **B.Sc. Software Engineering**

Faculty of Computer and Information Science, University of Ljubljana, Slovenia

### REFERENCES

Available upon request.